The build system that makes ship happen

Usage: turbo.exe [OPTIONS] [COMMAND]

Commands:
  bin           Get the path to the Turbo binary
  get-mfe-port  Get the port assigned to the current microfrontend
  completion    Generate the autocompletion script for the specified shell
  daemon        Runs the Turborepo background daemon
  devtools      Visualize your monorepo's package graph in the browser
  docs          Search the Turborepo documentation
  generate      Generate a new app / package
  telemetry     Enable or disable anonymous telemetry
  ls            EXPERIMENTAL: List packages in your monorepo
  link          Link your local directory to a Vercel organization and enable remote caching
  login         Login to your Vercel account
  logout        Logout to your Vercel account
  info          Print debugging information
  prune         Prepare a subset of your monorepo
  run           Run tasks across projects in your monorepo
  query         Query your monorepo using GraphQL. If no query is provided, spins up a GraphQL server with GraphiQL
  watch         Arguments used in run and watch
  unlink        Unlink the current directory from your Vercel organization and disable Remote Caching

Options:
      --version
          

      --skip-infer
          Skip any attempts to infer which version of Turbo the project is configured to use

      --no-update-notifier
          Disable the turbo update notification

      --api <API>
          Override the endpoint for API calls

      --color
          Force color usage in the terminal

      --cwd <CWD>
          The directory in which to run turbo

      --heap <HEAP>
          Specify a file to save a pprof heap profile

      --ui <UI>
          Specify whether to use the streaming UI or TUI

          Possible values:
          - tui:                                 Use the terminal user interface
          - stream:                              Use the standard output stream
          - stream-with-experimental-timestamps: Use the standard output stream with timestamps. Note: This feature is experimental and may change or be removed at any time
          - web:                                 Use the web user interface. Note: This feature is undocumented, experimental, and not meant to be used. It may change or be removed at any time

      --login <LOGIN>
          Override the login endpoint

      --no-color
          Suppress color usage in the terminal

      --preflight
          When enabled, turbo will precede HTTP requests with an OPTIONS request for authorization

      --remote-cache-timeout <TIMEOUT>
          Set a timeout for all HTTP requests

      --team <TEAM>
          Set the team slug for API calls

      --token <TOKEN>
          Set the auth token for API calls

      --trace <TRACE>
          Specify a file to save a pprof trace

      --verbosity <COUNT>
          Verbosity level. Useful when debugging Turborepo or creating logs for issue reports

      --experimental-otel-enabled [<ENABLED>]
          Enable OpenTelemetry metrics export
          
          [possible values: true, false]

      --experimental-otel-protocol <PROTOCOL>
          OTLP transport protocol (grpc or http-protobuf)

      --experimental-otel-endpoint <URL>
          OTLP collector endpoint URL

      --experimental-otel-timeout-ms <MILLISECONDS>
          OTLP export timeout in milliseconds (default: 10000)

      --experimental-otel-interval-ms <MILLISECONDS>
          OTLP export interval in milliseconds (default: 15000)

      --experimental-otel-header <KEY=VALUE>
          Add header to OTLP requests (can be repeated)

      --experimental-otel-resource <KEY=VALUE>
          Add resource attribute to metrics (can be repeated)

      --experimental-otel-metrics-run-summary [<METRICS_RUN_SUMMARY>]
          Emit run-level summary metrics (default: true)
          
          [possible values: true, false]

      --experimental-otel-metrics-task-details [<METRICS_TASK_DETAILS>]
          Emit per-task detail metrics (default: false)
          
          [possible values: true, false]

      --experimental-otel-use-remote-cache-token [<USE_REMOTE_CACHE_TOKEN>]
          Use remote cache token for OTLP authentication
          
          [possible values: true, false]

      --dangerously-disable-package-manager-check
          Allow for missing `packageManager` in `package.json`.
          
          `turbo` will use hints from codebase to guess which package manager should be used.

      --root-turbo-json <ROOT_TURBO_JSON>
          Use the `turbo.json` located at the provided path instead of one at the root of the repository

  -h, --help
          Print help (see a summary with '-h')

Run Arguments:
      --cache <CACHE>
          Set the cache behavior for this run. Pass a list of comma-separated key, value pairs to enable reading and writing to either the local or remote cache

      --force [<FORCE>]
          Ignore the existing cache (to force execution). Equivalent to `--cache=local:w,remote:w`
          
          [possible values: true, false]

      --remote-only [<REMOTE_ONLY>]
          Ignore the local filesystem cache for all tasks. Only allow reading and caching artifacts using the remote cache. Equivalent to `--cache=remote:rw`
          
          [possible values: true, false]

      --remote-cache-read-only [<REMOTE_CACHE_READ_ONLY>]
          Treat remote cache as read only. Equivalent to `--cache=remote:r;local:rw`
          
          [possible values: true, false]

      --no-cache
          Avoid saving task results to the cache. Useful for development/watch tasks. Equivalent to `--cache=local:r,remote:r`

      --cache-workers <CACHE_WORKERS>
          Set the number of concurrent cache operations (default 10)
          
          [default: 10]

      --dry-run [<DRY_RUN>]
          [possible values: text, json]

      --graph [<GRAPH>]
          Generate a graph of the task execution and output to a file when a filename is specified (.svg, .html, .mermaid, .dot). Outputs dot graph to stdout when no filename is provided. [DEPRECATED formats: .png, .jpg, .pdf, .json -- will be removed in 3.0]

      --daemon
          [DEPRECATED] The daemon is no longer used for `turbo run`. This flag will be removed in version 3.0

      --no-daemon
          [DEPRECATED] The daemon is no longer used for `turbo run`. This flag will be removed in version 3.0

      --profile [<PROFILE>]
          File to write turbo's performance profile output into. You can load the file up in chrome://tracing to see which parts of your build were slow

      --anon-profile [<ANON_PROFILE>]
          File to write turbo's performance profile output into. All identifying data omitted from the profile

      --summarize [<SUMMARIZE>]
          Generate a summary of the turbo run
          
          [possible values: true, false]

      --parallel
          [DEPRECATED] Execute all tasks in parallel. Use task configuration (`persistent`, `with`) instead

      --cache-dir <CACHE_DIR>
          Override the filesystem cache directory

      --concurrency <CONCURRENCY>
          Limit the concurrency of task execution. Use 1 for serial (i.e. one-at-a-time) execution

      --continue[=<CONTINUE>]
          Specify how task execution should proceed when an error occurs. Use "never" to cancel all tasks. Use "dependencies-successful" to continue running tasks whose dependencies have succeeded. Use "always" to continue running all tasks, even those whose dependencies have failed
          
          [default: never]
          [possible values: never, dependencies-successful, always]

      --single-package
          Run turbo in single-package mode

      --framework-inference [<BOOL>]
          Specify whether or not to do framework inference for tasks
          
          [default: true]
          [possible values: true, false]

      --global-deps <GLOBAL_DEPS>
          Specify glob of global filesystem dependencies to be hashed. Useful for .env and files

      --env-mode [<ENV_MODE>]
          Environment variable mode. Use "loose" to pass the entire existing environment. Use "strict" to use an allowlist specified in turbo.json

          Possible values:
          - loose:  Allow all environment variables for the process to be available
          - strict: Filter environment variables to only those that are specified in the `env` and `globalEnv` keys in `turbo.json`

  -F, --filter <FILTER>
          Use the given selector to specify package(s) to act as entry points. The syntax mirrors pnpm's syntax, and additional documentation and examples can be found in turbo's documentation https://turborepo.dev/docs/reference/command-line-reference/run#--filter

      --affected
          Filter to only packages that are affected by changes between the current branch and `main`

      --output-logs <OUTPUT_LOGS>
          Set type of process output logging. Use "full" to show all output. Use "hash-only" to show only turbo-computed task hashes. Use "new-only" to show only new output with only hashes for cached tasks. Use "none" to hide process output. (default full)

          Possible values:
          - full:        Displays all output
          - none:        Hides all task output
          - hash-only:   Show only the hashes of the tasks
          - new-only:    Only show output from cache misses
          - errors-only: Only show output from task failures

      --log-order <LOG_ORDER>
          Set type of task output order. Use "stream" to show output as soon as it is available. Use "grouped" to show output when a command has finished execution. Use "auto" to let turbo decide based on its own heuristics. (default auto)
          
          [possible values: auto, stream, grouped]

      --json
          Output machine-readable NDJSON to stdout instead of human-readable text. Disables the TUI and forces stream mode

      --log-file [<LOG_FILE>]
          Write structured JSON logs to a file. If no path is given, writes to `.turbo/logs/<epoch_millis>.json`

      --only
          Only executes the tasks specified, does not execute parent tasks

      --log-prefix <LOG_PREFIX>
          Use "none" to remove prefixes from task logs. Use "task" to get task id prefixing. Use "auto" to let turbo decide how to prefix the logs based on the execution environment. In most cases this will be the same as "task". Note that tasks running in parallel interleave their logs, so removing prefixes can make it difficult to associate logs with tasks. Use --log-order=grouped to prevent interleaving. (default auto)
          
          [default: auto]
          [possible values: auto, none, task]
